

123 Fourth Street, Raleigh, NC 12345 j.jameson@gmail.com (555) 555-5555 Senior project manager with over 13 years' experience coordinating complex projects, often involving B2B clients. Can oversee a project's staffing, budgetary and scheduling needs to ensure all expectations are met or exceeded. Able to communicate with clients' representatives and clearly relay their needs to a project's team. Creator of clear, achievable goals that result in desired deliverables.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **SENIOR PROJECT MANAGER**

CCC Social Outreach, Raleigh, NC I December 2011 - Present

- Oversee projects that deliver results to B2B clients, including social media overhauls and targeted advertising campaigns around product launches
- Work with and supervise web designers and developers,copywriters and graphic design professionals to set appropriate,achievable milestones
- Build detailed schedules and budget projections to develop affordable and realistic plans for timelines and expenses

#### **ASSISTANT PROJECT MANAGER**

ABC Digital Marketers. Raleigh, NC I July 2006 - November 2011

- Supported senior project managers by reviewing schedules and budgets and communicating with stakeholders when needed
- Served as quality-control agent on end products, including web graphics and marketing copy
- Ensured accurate Logging of employees' time and milestone completion dates

## **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN OPERATIONS MANAGEMENT

Raleigh Institute Of Business , Raleigh, NC | September 2001-June 2005

MASTER OF PROJECT MANAGEMENT

Raleigh Business University, Raleigh, NC I September 2005 - June 2007

## **KEY SKILLS**

- · Assessing projects' scope and objectives
- Properly allocating resources
- Professional interaction with clients and coworkers

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

- SmartSheet Certified Scheduler, 2020
- Certified PMI Project Management Professional, 2021